Blood will Reign
Hammer of the Gods is a history, action, adventure
film directed by Farren Blackburn.
Action epic sees a passionate young man transform into a brutal warrior as he travels the unforgiving landscape in search of
his long lost brother Hakan The Ferrocious, whose people are relying on him to restore order to their kingdom.
Steinar, played by Charlie Bewley.
Hagen, played by Clive Standen.
King Bagsecg, played by James Cosmo.
Hakan, played by Elliot Cowan.
Ivar, played by Ivan Kaye.
Grim, played by Michael Jibson.
Hammer of the Gods is a 2013 British action film directed by
Farren Blackburn and released on 5 July 2013.
In it, a dying Viking king sends his son on a quest to seek out his older
brother, the clan's only hope of defeating an approaching enemy horde.
The tone is dark.